Are you so over and not about Christmas, but also know that on that day you don't want to be by yourself?
Not a problem for just $5. You can join us over at the Seal Squad for our non-Christmas Christmas.
We'll ease into the day starting at noon.
Blending a cleanse. I found this nice little recipe that is multi-beneficial.
So we're going to talk about all the things and all the ways in which we can be beneficial to ourselves in the upcoming year.
At 4 o'clock, when everyone's sitting down for dinner, we're going to be sitting down to watch Sinners.
And I'm going to do a pause and play of giving my commentary for this classic film that was really the best part of 2025.
And then we're going to close out our night with a color and vibe.
Now, this is where I open the Zoom and everybody can join and get their crafts on and chit-chat or not chat, but basically just be in community.
That's right, y'all. On December 25th, we have a whole day of events at my Patreon that have nothing to do with Christmas.
You can come and hang out with us over at Patreon.
The Seal Squad is your community, baby.